Xavier University Academic Program Review records
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections
Xavier University Academic Program Review records
2002-2003
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections Phone: 513-745-4821 http://www.xavier.edu/cm/archives
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio)
1 linear feet (2 boxes)
This is a collection of program reviews submitted by Xavier University academic departments and offices as part of an overall review of the university in 2002-2003. These reviews were overseen by Dr. Mary Walker, Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs.
XUA-47
History of the Academic Program Review
The Academic Program Review was a university-wide study of academic departments and offices conducted in 2002-2003.
Each department and program was asked to supply information concerning its operations including its importance as it relates to the mission and vision of the university. The completed work of this review process was later used by the Xavier University Academic Planning Task Force to make a report judging the individual effectiveness of elements within the university community.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the various reviews submitted to the Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs by Xavier academic departments and administrative offices.
Not specified
Statement of Arrangement
The materials in this collection are arranged into the following general categories:
Preliminary Materials
Academic Program Review: University Programs
Academic Program Review: Williams College of Business
Academic Program Review: College of Arts and Sciences
Academic Program Review: College of Social Sciences
Academic Program Review: Administrative Programs
Related Material
For related documents, see also Xavier University Archives collections for the Planning Steering Committee (2002-03), found in Inactive Committee Records, XUA-36 and the Academic Planning Task Force records (XUA-46).
Restrictions on Access
Restricted access. Please contact the Xavier University Archives staff.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects:
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio)--Evaluation
Detailed Description of The Collection
- Academic Program Review Preliminary Materials (1 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Academic Program Review Preliminary Materials (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Academic Program Review: (Book 1 of 3) University Programs, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Academic Program Review (Book 1 of 3, continued) University Programs; Williams College of Business, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Academic Program Review (Book 1 of 3, continued) Williams College of Business, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Academic Program Review (Book 2 of 3) College of Arts and Sciences, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Academic Program Review (Book 2 of 3, continued) College of Arts and Sciences, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Academic Program Review (Book 2 of 3, continued) Colleges of Arts and Sciences, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Academic Program Review (Book 3 of 3) College of Social Sciences, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Academic Program Review (Book 3 of 3, continued) College of Social Sciences, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Academic Program Review (Book 3 of 3, continued) College of Social Sciences, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Academic Program Review Administrative Program Review (Folder 1), 2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Academic Program Review Administrative Program Review (Folder 2), 2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Administrative Program Reviews Division of Mission and Ministry, 2003 May (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Program reviews included in this Division of Mission & Ministry report are Ignatian Programs, Campus Ministry, Peace & Justice Programs, Service Fellowships, Mission & Ministry Internships, and Spirit Celebration.
- Academic Program Review Administrative Program Review Guide, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)